Andrew Westling

Software Engineer

Brooklyn, NY (646) 801-0105 a@andrewwestling.com github.com/expandrew linkedin.com/in/andrewwestling

Overview

Design-minded web application engineer. Background in architecture.

Specialization in JavaScript single-page applications and UI/design-system development. Handy with the usual infrastructure and build tools.

AngularJS, Sass/SCSS/LESS/CSS, Node.js, webpack, grunt/gulp, React, Django, Python, Docker, git, Shell scripting, AWS, CircleCl, Heroku, Rails, HTML5, Foundation, Bootstrap.

Experience

Architizer / Software Engineer

Sept 2015 - present, New York City

Full-stack feature development for Architizer's marketplace for building-products. Some projects I've worked on:

- Built a UI design / component library to speed up feature development
- Built a messaging interface to enable communication on the marketplace
- Built a new directory UI for architects to search for building-products
- Migrated a bespoke front-end JS framework into React to make it easier to maintain
- Tightened up infrastructure to reduce downtime risks and speed up deployments

Primary tools: AngularJS, React, SCSS, Django, Docker, CircleCI, and AWS

EyeCue Lab / Software Engineer

Oct 2014 - Sept 2015, Portland, Oregon

Built marketing pages and features for web applications using Rails and AngularJS in an agency setting. Delivered three client projects while working at EyeCue Lab.

Apple / AppleCare Advisor

June 2013 - May 2014, Eugene, Oregon

Technical phone support and customer service for macOS products, Apple ID, fraud/billing, and iTunes Store purchase issues.

Education

Epicodus

Summer 2014, Portland, Oregon

Code school. Ruby on Rails and JavaScript. Learned via test-driven development and daily pair programming. Internship-to-hire with EyeCue Lab after Epicodus.

University of Oregon / B.Arch, Architecture

2009-2014, Eugene, Oregon

Graduated with Bachelor of Architecture degree from UO School of Architecture. Member of UO Symphony Orchestra.